MY BIAS, MY BOSS
That's my house right there.
It's late. You should go home.
But we're almost there.
Why would you...
I'll walk you to your house.
No need,
thank you for walking me home.
You should go home. Thank you.
It's slippery.
- If you don't watch out...
- Mr. Kang!
I was worried you'd end up hurt
if you weren't careful.
If anything...
this seems more dangerous.
I'm sorry.
I should get going.
Take care on your way home. Goodbye.
EPISODE 3
This seems more dangerous.
I did save him from danger...
but did I offend him somehow?
Still, I saved his life.
He was being too cold.
Ms. Nam!
No.
Mr. Kang!
I was worried you'd end up hurt
if you weren't careful.
What's this?
What's wrong with my heart?
Do I have a heart problem?
Mr. Kang, have this and cheer up.
Good luck.
Mr. Kang, do you drink coffee now?
I thought you didn't drink coffee.
What's gotten into you?
Coffee...
Right.
It's the coffee.
I shouldn't have had it.
It's just the coffee.
Appello.
The Outstanding Employee
of the Year is...
Gosh, it's nerve-wracking.
The winner is...
Congratulations.
It goes to...
Me?
Come on.
Kang...
Ha...
Gi!
KANG HA-GI
No way.
FLIGHT TICKET TO NEW YORK
No...
This can't be true.
What...
Wait!
Mr. Kang, you're the CEO.
You can't pick yourself.
I'm also an employee of Appello.
That's still not fair.
You know how hard I worked.
I worked harder.
You shouldn't abuse your power
for personal gain like this.
What did you say?
"Personal gain"?
Ms. Nam, how much do you know?
No, I...
- The thing is...
- Actually, forget it.
As of this moment, you're fired.
What?
I said you're fired.
You're fired.
No!
What was that?
A premonition?
No, no way.
It was just a meaningless dream.
What on earth?
What's with the weather?
Man, things are flying everywhere.
Our stage!
We've got unexpected heavy rain.
Roads are closed,
and the winds are out of control.
The brand CEOs might have
a hard time making it.
Right, we'll probably be
the first to arrive.
How bad is the damage?
Do we have confirmation yet?
I'm afraid we won't know for sure
until we see it in person.
Mr. Kang.
Get the security personnel
in place first.
Tie down or clear out any equipment
that might shift or fall.
Yes, sir.
Wait. Mr. Kang.
Who already did all this?
Mr. Kang.
Someone covered everything
with tarps here too.
The CEOs haven't arrived yet,
have they?
Yes, who could've done all this?
Wait. Mr. Kang, isn't that...
Who's that over there?
Mr. Kang.
Hello?
You've arrived?
Wait there for a moment.
Mr. Kang, the employees have arrived.
I'll be right back. Please wait here.
I have to save the clothes at least.
Ms. Nam?
Mr. Kang, you're here.
- What are you doing here alone?
- Oh, the clothes.
They're the vendors' assets.
I'm trying to salvage what I can.
Jeez.
Do you realize
how dangerous it is out here?
Why would you be here alone?
I'm sorry. I was in a rush.
Let's wrap this up fast
and get somewhere safe.
Okay.
No!
It's dangerous. Stay away, Ms. Nam.
Let's do this together.
Move over there.
Now that we're holding it together
it's not shaking anymore.
Look, the wind is dying down.
I'm sure the rain will stop soon too.
Let's cheer up just a bit more.
How can you be
smiling at a time like this?
You've got to smile
when things get tough.
Don't you know
smiling actually makes things better?
Mr. Kang, we're here.
Let me put this on you.
Good.
Two, three.
Here. Enjoy.
- Have some bread while you work.
- Okay.
Does this need to go up?
Should we set it up? Two, three.
Press it down. One, two, three.
Don't put yourself in danger
like that again.
Safety comes first.
Yes, sir.
Still, I do...
appreciate your intentions.
Excuse me?
- What did you just say?
- I mean...
Nothing. I'm just saying.
Is everything okay?
It's delicious.
Maybe because it's soaked in tears...
I mean, rainwater.
No, I didn't mean that bread.
Never mind.
- Careful.
- Okay.
It's not exactly
that we're canceling.
If you could just
give us some time...
No, that's enough.
We'll consider this discussion over.
- But...
- Sir, you can't leave like this.
Sir. Ma'am. Wait.
- We're done.
- Wait.
What's going on?
BRB backed out of the contract.
So did Saucebody, Sweetheart
and 9203 too.
I personally called the CEOs
not to worry.
They somehow heard a rumor
about the Appello fashion show
getting canceled
and came to see for themselves.
Looks like
SE leaked some info.
They're signing with SE instead.
Unless our information is sent to SE
in real time
it's hard to find out.
Sir, you don't think the spy is...
Would a spy be out here
since dawn working that hard?
Being here since dawn means
they could get the info faster.
- Gosh. Mr. Young-woo, this.
- Okay.
Here you go.
Clear things up here.
I think it's pretty much done.
I'm going elsewhere.
Finish that up.
I can't believe
all this is going to waste.
At least we managed
to salvage these clothes.
Everyone worked so hard
on preparing this.
Sir.
Are you okay?
I heard
you salvaged our clothes
by covering them with tarps.
Thank you so much.
What happens to those clothes now?
They were meant for on-site sales
at the fashion show.
I suppose
they'll just sit in inventory.
It's ending
before I even get started.
I haven't given up yet.
Excuse me?
It's not over until it's truly over.
Will you trust me
and follow my lead one last time?
Guys, the moment you've all been
waiting for is finally here.
For today's Morning Greetings...
I actually took a shower this morning
because of this guest.
It's the busiest actor
and fashion director these days.
His name literally means "Two cold."
It's Lee Chan. Welcome.
Two, three. We're destiny.
Hello, I'm Lee Chan from D.N.X.
It's nice to meet you.
DJ AN YOUNG-MI
You're still using that greeting?
You've been using it
since you debuted as an idol, right?
Right. But since no one
calls me that anymore
I keep it alive myself.
Do you ever find yourself
wanting to go back
to your D.N.X days?
Of course.
I know a lot of fans are
still waiting.
How are the other members
doing lately?
They all seem to be doing well
in their own lanes.
We always talk about reuniting
someday for sure.
Really? That's going to be
great news for your fans.
On that note, our first song today
will be Dear My Light
from D.N.X's final album.
- Oh, my.
- Jeez.
Are you out of your mind?
How can you hide something like this?
- Calm down.
- Chan.
You can't do this here!
What is it? Say something.
- Get off me!
- Calm down already.
Come on.
- Hey.
- Get off!
- Don't do this to Roy.
- Stop.
- Move. Get out of my way!
- Don't do this too.
- I said, move!
You're no different.
The two of you ruined
everything we built!
ROY, LEAVE THE GROUP
D.N.X OFFICIALLY ANNOUNCES DISBANDING
Hey.
I'm just getting better at lying.
What was that?
No, nothing.
I CRIED SO MUCH TODAY, BUT I'M FINE
THESE AREN'T TEARS OF SADNESS
BUT SUPPORT FOR YOUR NEW START
I BELIEVE I'LL GET TO SEE YOU
SHINE ON STAGE AGAIN
What? What exactly do you mean, sir?
The Appello fashion show
- will proceed tomorrow as planned.
- What?
We already took a big loss. Are you
suggesting we rebuild the stage?
Yes, we must do it.
If the participating brands suffer,
who'd ever want to partner with us?
If we lose them here...
losing the market to SE will only be
a matter of time.
Is there even a place
we can use right away?
Right here.
- Here?
- Yes.
- We'll do an online show.
- What?
We'll use this space as the runway.
We'll set up four stationary cameras
and focus on the looks
against a white backdrop.
Given how small the space is,
won't it look a bit too plain?
The clothes might actually
stand out more.
Our whole thing was an open-air show
accessible to everyone.
It's such a shame.
It's not just a shame.
It's a huge letdown.
We'll have to redirect the audience
to the livestream.
I know this is far from ideal
but keeping our promise
to the partner brands takes priority.
You're right.
How about projection mapping?
Director Lee?
Every brand in this show has
its own concept, right?
We could visualize their keywords
and shift the space's mood.
The models would be walking
in the same studio
but the background
would constantly feel new.
You mean, use the white walls
as screens for a stage?
Right.
That would bring out
each brand's vibe much better.
Can we prepare that in a day?
I have a few references on hand.
Shall we start
matching the outfits then?
Good. Let's get things prepared
as soon as possible
and run another rehearsal tonight.
Let's get to work right away.
- Yes, sir.
- Clear things out quickly.
We're out of time.
Let's pick up the pace.
Looks like we need
to clear this entire area.
Be careful.
One moment.
Sales and Logistics,
prioritize setting up
- the online show equipment.
- Where are you going? Take these.
This concept is too dark.
Planning and Merchandising,
back up Director Lee.
- A bit...
- Get him
whatever feedback,
info, or items he needs.
Hello, sir. We're doing
an online fashion show...
Marketing, you'll be the busiest.
Announce the transition
across all official Appello socials
and notify the partner brands.
Pull keywords for each brand too.
Ms. Kim, the notice is up
on the website.
- Okay.
- The keyword visual aid is done too.
Ms. Da-reum, run that over
to the studio quickly.
Yes, ma'am.
Here you go.
That's our Director Chan.
I like it.
Add sunglasses to this look.
He's so cool.
I hear you're diving
into the fashion business.
Yes. Going forward,
I plan to incorporate the philosophy
of "Unframe,"
which is to break out of the box.
Stiff and standardized fashion
is boring.
I'd really love
to work with him someday.
Everyone dresses similarly
these days.
Even the standards
for being fashionable are similar.
I want to shatter those standards.
We're actually working together now.
It's crazy.
Gosh. I heard you were out there
since dawn cleaning up the site.
I didn't even think of that.
The CEO is different indeed.
Even our newest employee was there.
- I see.
- Okay.
Was she too busy to call me?
- What?
Nothing.
Whoever it is, their dedication
to the company is remarkable.
- We'll refer to this.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
I think so.
Anyway, tomorrow is the problem.
I have to head out
for a shoot right now.
I'll take care
of the fashion show somehow.
- Let's work this out.
- Okay.
- See you.
- Bye. Let's be in touch.
Wait, Chan is leaving.
Was I gazing happily at Chan
in this mess?
Jeez, I look like an absolute wreck.
MOM
- Aren't you having lunch?
- Let me step out briefly.
- Goodness.
- Gosh, excuse me.
Taxi.
SE CORPORATION
ONLY YOU, PARK SEO-JIN
Please drive a little faster.
Thank you.
It's Mom.
Jeez, this is crazy.
Mom!
- Mom.
- Da-reum?
What brings you here?
I came to see my daughter, of course.
- Come with me.
- What?
You can't just drop by like this
without giving me a heads-up.
Wait, Da-reum.
Do you go to work dressed like that?
Why?
Jeez, you're frumpy and messy.
Look at yourself.
I don't normally dress this poorly.
Something came up.
Anyway, go now.
You're good
now that you saw me, right?
- Go on and leave.
- What... Wait.
Wait up.
Take this.
You didn't have to bring this.
It's heavy.
It's your favorite jangjorim.
I packed just a little for you.
What about the rice cakes
I sent the other day?
Did you share them
with your coworkers?
What did they say?
Well, they...
They loved them.
Right?
I lined up at a famous rice cake shop
from 5 a.m. just to order those.
Mom, I...
The truth is, SE Corporation...
What is it?
Has work been tough lately?
That's not it.
That's how corporate life is.
It's hard on everyone.
But you know
I'm always rooting for you, right?
Mom.
I'm sorry.
Oh, hush now.
I should get going.
It's almost time for my bus.
Let me walk with you.
I'll catch you a cab.
I met the CEO of BRB.
He already signed with SE.
Darn SE.
I wish this building
would just collapse.
- What's wrong?
- Hold on. Let me send you something.
I'm hanging up.
- Thank you.
- What...
You work at SE, right?
I'm running late for an appointment.
Take this.
Here.
- What...
- Wait a second.
Is that how you dress at work?
What do you do with your paycheck?
Dress up a little, okay?
What the...
Let's go.
But that's my taxi.
This is outrageous.
COCOTALK
TEAM MANAGER CHOI SEONG-WOOK
This is Ms. Nam Da-reum, right?
She's not secretly meeting
Director Kim of SE, is she?
Where's Ms. Nam?
She stepped out saying,
"Let me step out briefly."
- Ms. Nam.
- Yes?
Where have you been?
I had urgent business
so I stepped out briefly
during lunch.
What kind of business?
Well...
A friend wanted to see me real quick.
I don't know what you've been
going around getting
but it's a basic rule
to report when leaving the office
even during a lunch break.
Don't you know that?
Is the company a joke to you?
I apologize.
Listen up, new hires.
Stop assisting for the fashion show
and go back to your regular duties.
We've got things under control now.
And the office needs a skeleton crew.
Mr. Kang.
Can't I help with the show
until the end?
I've been on this
since the rehearsals.
I want to see it through.
Ms. Nam.
Didn't you hear me?
Stay out of it.
Mr. Kang is too harsh.
I mean, you cared enough to rush out
to the site at the crack of dawn.
Are you okay, Ms. Da-reum?
I'm all right.
We're promoting it on socials
and pop-up windows
but how many will actually see it?
Exactly.
Don't you get the feeling
that the online fashion show
is going to flop quietly?
What do we do?
Guys.
Why don't we try doing something?
- Oh, wow.
Ms. Da-reum, you're good at it.
Why do you care so much
about this show, Ms. Da-reum?
Seeing everyone work so hard on-site
made me promise myself
that I'd do my absolute best
to ensure this show's success.
You're so cool.
You can do it, Ms. Da-reum.
Time to put all my fangirl skills
to good use!
Could you make a few adjustments
to the model?
The lighting's too bright
with too much glare on the clothes.
Please adjust that as well.
Will do.
Mr. Kang.
Take a look at this.
We went from this...
OUR FASHION SHOW IS ON AS PLANNED
...to this.
APPELLO IN NAMSAN
OUR
FASHION SHOW
IS ON
AS PLANNED
TRADITION NEVER DIES
THOSE DAYS, THAT FEEL
WEAR CLOTHES OF TOMORROW
NOVEMBER 13, 6:00 P.M., LIVE
What is this?
The rookies made it
to promote the online show.
Isn't it fun?
How about we post it
on our official account?
It's fun.
Whose idea was this?
Nam Da-reum's.
It was Ms. Nam's?
Yes.
Ms. Kim.
Did Ms. Da-reum
handle any sensitive info
regarding the fashion show?
No.
We don't put a rookie in charge
of anything too important.
Why? Is there a problem?
Come with me.
There's something I didn't tell you.
Yes?
Ms. Da-reum.
She worked at SE Corporation.
Yes, I know that.
- You knew that?
- Yes.
She told me she used to work there.
It wasn't on her resume.
She was there for under two months
and thought it would look bad.
She couldn't stand the place
and waited for us
to post about a vacancy.
She didn't even tell her family yet.
Her mom went to SE Corporation
to bring her a lunch box today.
Where are you coming from?
Mr. Kang reviewed the clip you made.
Regarding uploading it
to our official account...
it's a go!
He told me to tell you
you did so well.
Plus, you can all help out
with tomorrow's fashion show.
Can we really?
Post that video on our account,
then go home.
- Okay!
- Thank you.
You did so well.
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
Bye.
Come on.
Let's go upstairs.
- Hyeok.
- Hey.
- You go ahead.
- Okay.
It's been so long.
- Do you have a shoot?
- Sorry?
I was invited on a variety show.
- To do what?
- A bit of this and that.
That's great.
- I owe it to you.
- I didn't do anything.
If you mention D.N.X on the radio
I get to go on TV and reminisce.
Thanks a lot.
"We want
to get back together one day."
Are you serious?
I guess
it takes a lot to be an actor.
I saw
the video you made.
Earlier on
I made a mistake.
Sorry. I had my earphones in.
What did you just say?
Never mind.
Are you just getting off work?
Yes.
Let me ask you something.
Did you work somewhere
before joining Appello?
Before I joined Appello?
I worked at SE Corporation briefly.
Director Kim Han-chul of SE.
Do you know him well?
Director Kim?
I greeted him a few times
when we met?
That's it. Why do you ask?
And actually
I went to SE Corporation
earlier today.
My mom thinks I still work there.
She brought me some food.
I apologize.
I'll report to you
before I go anywhere now.
Okay. It's late.
Get back safely.
Can I do it?
These heels are pretty low.
I think these will be okay.
We must smile even more
when things are tough.
Don't you know
that smiling
actually makes things better?
Any special reason
why you came to Appello?
Actually
I wanted to learn more about myself.
Instead of just getting
more qualifications
I wanted to find out
what I truly love.
That was why I chose
to come to a place I was drawn to.
I should've given it more time.
I'm awake again.
The video...
8.1 MILLION VIEWS
THE ONE WHO DID THIS IS THE BEST
THIS IS HOW THEY DO A FASHION SHOW
I LIKE APPELLO'S STYLE
APPELLO ONLINE FASHION SHOW
Chan joined in?
No way!
NOW THIS IS WHAT YOU CALL BEING HIP
EXPECTATIONS ARE THROUGH THE ROOF
OUR
FASHION SHOW
IS ON
AS PLANNED
Thanks to Director Lee
and his ten million followers
our runway challenge clip
got a huge response.
Our app downloads
and social media visitors
greatly increased, as you can see.
Keep an eye on the numbers
so that response
- actually helps us.
- Yes, sir.
Marketing did a good job too.
- Thank you.
Let's wrap this up, then.
- Sir.
- Okay.
Mr. Won-tae, bring those materials
to my desk quickly.
Okay, will do.
Ms. Seo, why don't you
film a challenge video?
I'm not interested.
We're five minutes out.
- Mr. Kang.
- Thanks.
APPELLO ONLINE FASHION SHOW CUE SHEET
5:45 P.M. REMOVE FLOOR MARKERS
Okay, everyone.
It's time to finish up.
Hat, sneakers.
You're clear.
Ms. Kim,
we're almost ready backstage.
Okay.
- Did you test the stills?
- That's all done.
Okay, one minute to go.
Stand by.
Music.
Cue.
ONLINE FASHION SHOW SOUNDS AMAZING
PERFECT LIGHTING, MUSIC, AND OUTFITS
VIEWERS INCREASING
MS. SEO
POST LINK FOR CLOTHES AND SHOES!
We have many more viewers
than expected.
- And it's still increasing.
- Conversion to sales?
Looking good.
Go.
Looking good. Okay.
LIVE CHAT
How much stock do we have?
LIVE SHOW HAS ENDED
PLEASE WAIT WHILE WE PREPARE THE VOD
Okay, the show is over!
- Gosh.
- Good job.
Listen up, everyone!
About 80,000 watched the show live.
It was a massive hit!
Great job, Mr. Kang.
A hug?
- Well done.
- Hey!
Ms. Nam.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for wearing our products
to film the online challenge.
Your clothes are beautiful.
I bet your brand
will have so many new fans.
You say the sweetest things. Thanks.
- I have to thank the others.
- Sure.
Mr. Kang.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
Sir.
How did that feel?
Mr. Kang.
I feel so pleased and proud.
- Ms. Da-reum.
- Yes?
Spare me some time tomorrow.
I have something to say.
What?
REAL-TIME GOAL AND PERFORMANCE
REAL-TIME APPELLO STATS
CRISIS BECOMES AN OPPORTUNITY
APPELLO'S NEW FASHION SHOW FORMAT
REACHES 80,000 VIEWERS
WATCH APPELLO'S SHOW AT HOME
Come in.
You're still here.
I have some things to check.
You can go ahead.
Okay.
You did really well today, Mr. Kang.
Seong-wook.
You did well too.
You did more.
Hey, neighbor.
You bought that to share, right?
Toss the trash and come on up.
Just you wait.
Do you have snacks?
What? An online fashion show?
Your challenge thing was everywhere,
so I checked it out.
It did pretty well for something
that was done last minute.
We didn't do too bad, fortunately.
Crisis averted, I guess.
Then why the long face?
What is it? What's wrong?
There is...
this employee who works really hard.
I thought the employee
was a corporate spy.
Are you in a spy flick?
The circumstances
seemed very suspicious.
I don't have to see what happened.
You were your usual self.
I bet you spewed some nasty stuff
with the frigidity of Arctic winds.
Is it a girl?
- Is she pretty?
- Jeez.
If she's pretty,
apologize twice over.
Hey.
I should...
- apologize, right?
- The sooner, the better.
Apologies expire too.
They mean nothing
if you wait too long.
- Luni.
- Yes? You called?
Not so loud.
Speak quietly.
Well
I need to say sorry.
How should I do that?
What kind of sorry do you mean?
Are you feeling bad for someone?
Or will you mend a relationship?
It's the latter, obviously.
Search results
on how to mend a relationship.
One, acknowledge your mistake
with all honesty.
Two, tell them sincerely
that you're sorry.
Can you put some passion
into your answer?
Anyone can say what you said.
It's so boring and basic.
Do you have to apologize
because you said something mean?
Then how about you practice
saying nice things first?
What? Nice things?
HABIT OF SPEAKING NICELY
Speak nicely.
Hey, Ms. Da-reum.
You look nice today, as always.
What?
I mean...
Your cup looks nice.
Oh, thanks.
My cup.
It's all going wrong.
Ms. Da-reum.
About that day...
Excuse me.
Sorry, I have to be at the warehouse.
- I have to dash.
- But I...
It's so hard to apologize.
Oh, my gosh.
You don't have to do that.
Thank you so very much.
I'll get back at you for your help
next season. Wait and see.
- You promised.
- You bet I did.
- Here you go.
- Just one box at a time?
- Who am I working for?
- Take this already.
My shoulders hurt.
That's all done.
Goodbye, then. Thank you!
- Good job.
- Bye, sir.
Work harder, Young-woo.
I'm not a slacker.
He got me all wrong.
Oh, right. I have to head back
to work on the presentation.
- I'll come with you.
- Okay.
I have to work late.
I have to head home.
- What?
Before I started here, I said
I'd build you a skyscraper.
It's hard work putting on
just one event.
That thing up there.
I want it so much.
The banner?
No.
That face.
Director.
- Do you want it?
- What?
That face.
Be gentle, if you don't mind.
Please.
What do you need this for anyway?
It'll cost a fortune to throw out.
Oh, well...
It's to prevent her from quitting.
I want her to stay.
That trick
works on her, you see.
I have the answer!
Mr. Kang.
Do you...
have a task for her?
No. Get back to work.
I think you do.
Work.
What are you doing
at the office this late at night?
I came here to see you.
To complain.
At me?
Why didn't you call?
I waited to hear from you.
Were you that busy
with the fashion show?
Yes.
I wanted to buy you a meal.
There are too many eyes
and ears here.
I wanted to meet with you alone.
Are you keeping your distance
because I'm your superior?
No, it's not that.
- No?
- No.
Then...
give me your number.
Here you go.
DA-REUM
It's so strange.
What is?
That I'm
sitting here, chatting with you.
I think it's strange how we met.
Why is that?
I'm just one of your many fans.
I may have many fans
but I don't meet them all like this.
I don't have the chance to.
I see.
I'd like to know
how you became my fan.
- How?
- Yes, how.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, NAM DA-REUM
Let's get a pastry.
- I'll buy you one.
- Great.
- You will?
- Yes.
Can I eat more than one?
What were you like
in high school, Chan?
In high school?
I didn't stand out. I was quiet.
Before I knew it, I was invisible.
People acted like I wasn't there
and that was harder
than actually being bullied.
If someone had said
just one word to me
going to school would've hurt less.
If anyone out there
is going through the same thing
I hope they remember this.
You may feel alone right now
but someone will appear one day
to love you.
They did for me.
Until then
I want to tell them to hang in there.
That's my message.
Hi.
Do you like D.N.X too?
Yes.
Nice to meet you, comrade.
Okay, so...
My D.N.X bias
is Roy. Who is your favorite?
Just so you know, I love Hyeok.
My bias
is Lee Chan.
- It's Lee Chan.
- We don't overlap.
That's why you have his merch.
Hey, isn't this really rare?
Can I have a look?
- Yes.
- Oh, wow. Thanks.
- Look!
- It's so cute.
It's so cute.
My gosh. It's adorable.
Look at this. I wish I had this.
They are my best friends to this day.
That must've been so tough.
Your songs got me
through my worst times.
And they brought
my best friends to me
so I could enjoy
the rest of high school.
That's why
I'm always grateful to you.
You held up well.
And grew up well.
But
is that it?
There could be other reasons.
My good looks. My cool persona.
My charms.
That's a give...
It's a given.
There's no one else like you
with such perfect looks
and a great character.
That's what I'm like on TV.
I could be completely different.
I could be fake.
I could be a hypocrite.
You are a good person.
I adored you for 12 years.
I can tell that much.
If you tried to be
a good person so far
that alone makes you a good person.
Long-standing fans are grateful
that you didn't get into any trouble.
You didn't drink and drive or gamble.
I mean it.
I'm really so proud of you.
Are you? Thanks.
Thank you.
No, it's not messy. I was gentle.
Are you sure?
I'll do it.
It's better.
I had it taken care of.
- Chan.
- What?
Keep it a secret that I'm your fan.
- All of a sudden?
- Please...
Then grant me a wish.
What? Okay, fine, whatever.
I'll think of a wish, Da-reum.
Okay?
"Da-reum"?
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
EPILOGUE
Hey, Chan.
We got the theme for the photoshoot.
I'm tired.
Don't you need a look?
These are the questions for when
- you meet your fans...
- Later.
Okay.
- If you're in a bad mood...
- I'm tired and you're noisy.
I think an actor
should check this out.
That would help.
That's how you become successful.
FASHION SHOW IS ON
AS PLANNED
- Hey.
- What is it?
Let's film a challenge video.
You just said you were tired.
- We must do it now.
- Right now?
Action. One, two, three.
You're moving way too fast.
Slow down.
Let's try that once more.
Let's do this.
SPECIAL THANKS TO CHANG HYAE-JIN,
HUR JUNG-DO, AN YOUNG-MI
Don't be so weak.
You're carrying your Chan.
Are you jealous?
We're at work.
I'm worried people will talk.
A date? What should I do?
Is it a gift for someone you like?
Let's go to my place.
Will you go as a woman or as a fan?
No! Ms. Nam!
That she likes me.
A head-on
romance?